[{'question': 'Which of the following designs make a site more understandable?', 'answer': 'Make content appear and operate in predictable ways.'}, {'question': 'Which of the following designs make a site more operable?', 'answer': 'Do not use content that causes seizures. '}, {'question': 'Web Accessibility is ____________________.', 'answer': 'about making the web available to as many people as possible'}, {'question': 'Which of the following statements is TRUE?', 'answer': 'Consideration of web accessibility will require web designers to make it easier for users from different countries to use a site.   '}, {'question': '____________________ uses the inhaling and exhaling of air to interact with a computer interface.', 'answer': 'Sip and Puff Switch'}, {'question': '___________________ is an important tool that helps people with visual impairment to browse web pages. ', 'answer': 'Screen reader'}, {'question': 'Users with hearing impairments are ________________________.', 'answer': 'unable to decipher sound adequately'}, {'question': '____________________ is a tactile system of raised dots that is read with the fingers.', 'answer': 'Braille'}, {'question': 'Design trends can be followed if _________________.', 'answer': 'the competition is also adopting the trending design '}, {'question': 'Designs can use ________________ to add character and differentiation into a minimalist style.', 'answer': 'chatbots'}, {'question': 'Gestures are essentially controls and interactions that are ________________.', 'answer': 'implemented with better tactile feedback than physical controls'}, {'question': 'The gesture of �spread� has often being used to implement ________________.', 'answer': 'zooming-in when viewing photos'}, {'question': 'An old man is struggling to browse on an e-commerce site to buy a new bicycle for his grandson. He is unable to see the words on the web page as they are very small.', 'answer': 'Yes, it should. The design could have used a larger font or allow the user to increase the font size if needed.'}, {'question': 'A sales reporting website of a company is used by all of its distributors without complaints for many years. By following a recent design trend, the users can save one mouse click in the entire revamped workflow. What could be the strongest reason to avoid using the trending design?', 'answer': 'The benefit may not be significant enough for existing users to embrace the new design.'}, {'question': 'Original illustrations have helped to push up the visitor numbers for some sites. However, they should be avoided if ____________________.', 'answer': "they are irrelevant to the user's intended workflow"}, {'question': 'A page design using a carousel that automatically displays the next item in 2 seconds may not have good accessibility because ________________.', 'answer': 'some users may not have enough time to read the item'}, {'question': 'A visible grid of simple borders and frames on a webpage ___________________________.', 'answer': 'help distinguish one section from another'}, {'question': 'Which of the following development decision will aid the users of screen readers?', 'answer': 'Allow home page video to autoplay on page load '}, {'question': 'Elements on a web page should not flash more than ___________________________.', 'answer': '3 times per second'}, {'question': 'Users with speech impairments are ________________________.', 'answer': 'unable to speak and use voice commands'}, {'question': 'Descriptive audio is intended to assist users with ____________________ to better understand the content of videos.', 'answer': 'visual impairment'}, {'question': 'List view may be chosen over card-based layout if ________________.', 'answer': 'content items need to be compared and scanned quickly'}, {'question': 'Which of the following is the most descriptive headline?', 'answer': '"Robots to help elderly clean their houses."'}, {'question': 'Which of the following action can improve web accessibility?', 'answer': 'Keep navigation mechanism consistent across pages on a website.'}, {'question': '__________ is an assistive technology that ignores brief or repeated keystrokes.', 'answer': 'StickyKeys'}, {'question': 'Which of the following designs make a site more robust?', 'answer': 'Maximize compatibility with current and future user tools.'}, {'question': 'Which statement best describes the characteristic of using video background?', 'answer': 'Video can provide good contrast to display headlines.'}, {'question': 'Hamburger button can reduce the usability of a design because ________________.', 'answer': 'it hides the available options from the user'}, {'question': 'Card-based interface are popular on many websites because ____________________.', 'answer': 'the interface organizes possible interactions within identifiable containers'}, {'question': 'Which of the following design is not improving keyboard accessibility?', 'answer': 'Ensure keyboard focus is hidden'}, {'question': 'It is not a good idea to use colour as the only feedback indicator because ____________________.', 'answer': 'there may be users who are colour blind'}, {'question': 'Which of the following designs make a site more preceivable?', 'answer': 'Help users avoid and correct mistakes.'}, {'question': 'What is a typographic hero image?', 'answer': 'It is a large banner image prominently placed on a web page that has reduced or eliminated imaginery, with focus on text arrangement and style.'}, {'question': 'According to the Web Content Accessibility Guideline, in order to conform to Level AAA in terms of Visual Presentation, one of the success criteria is that the  _________________.', 'answer': 'width is not more than 100 characters or glyphs'}]